Hello friends, in this video I will tell you how you can easily pay ICICI bank loan nobody amount
on phone on google or from bank account, so here friends
open the phone and make the payment after opening on the phone Here the icon of Two Bank UPI ID
is forbidden, you have to click on it, after clicking on it, here is the UPI ID, friends, you have to
note it down, hello, write it in small, lonz, then put it on the back seat, WhatsApp After that
you will have to write your full loan account number personal loan account number or home loan account number whatever your
car loan account number or vehicle loan account number you have to enter the full alphanumeric number like alepo that
nopd APN in this way OPD then after this 0004 I pay for this personal loan, here
you have to type the full account number in this way whatever people you are running or whatever loan you have but you do
n't have the account number you have to type in full After which write A Great ICICI, don't
write bank, then here it went to the IDIO UPI ID launch dot complete loan account number 88 then what is shown below
you have to click on UPSIDC friends after clicking it will look like this
Have to verify, after verifying, see here loan and name will come, your and nick name is optional,
you can write whatever you want, you can do this, I am writing in minimum ICICI overdue and
setting it, after that you have to also have to do from after shift to here inter amount then amount
whatever is audio amount here you have to pay here by typing this friends UPI ID like here
option came on phone I in the same way on your Google Also UPI ID option comes and on bank
means if you use net banking then UPI ID option comes there too, so in the same way
you have to note UPI ID even if you pay it through any medium on Google on phone You can now back it
up after it appears, after backing up you have to click on the history, after clicking on which the
stomach is now showing the moon of 1514 here, this is the transaction ID here and the UTR number of the bank account
here You can take screenshot from this video so friends subscribe the channel and I have
made videos on loan process repayment schedule loan statement of many banks, to watch the video
subscribe the channel in which I have uploaded finance and KYC quit Muslim videos Have done
if you want to take this loan friends here I have given the contact number then you
can contact me minimum salary is 25000 we are doing this in pan india location note mostly
on your metro cities we do it then get it hoon main video jai hind friends thank you